<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Politics Game</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="play">Play</string>
    <string name="info">Info</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="game_title">Game Title</string>
    <string name="title_activity_setup">SetupActivity</string>
    <string name="aiToggle">Debug: AI Toggle</string>
    <string name="countryName">Country Name</string>
    <string name="economic">Economically:</string>
    <string name="social">Socially:</string>
    <string name="government_type">Government Type</string>
    <string name="gameplay_help">Gameplay Help</string>
    <string name="gameplay_intro">Welcome to Politics Game. In this game you must take control of a newly elected government in a fictional country. You will be faced with a series of events that lead you from your first month in office to the next General Election. You must decide how your political party will react to these events and maintain a balance between three key resources.</string>
    <string name="gameplay_approval">Approval Rating - A measurement of how happy the public are with your government. Maintaining a high approval is no easy task, you must keep enough voters happy if you wish to be elected again. </string>
    <string name="gameplay_budget">Budget - The amount of public money you have to spend. This will be used to fund everything, from infrastructure to your next election campaign. Ensure that you always have enough, a disaster may always be around the corner. </string>
    <string name="gameplay_stability">Stability Level - The stability of your own political party. How can a government achieve anything if it is plagued by internal squabbles? Keep a close eye on this level, some events may send your government spiralling out of control of the country. Keep your back-benchers happy.</string>
    <string name="gameplay_gamestart">When you begin a new game you must enter a name for your country and select the type of government you would like to have. This will alter your starting situation and make it easier or harder to gain a particular resource. Have a different experience every time with 9 unique archetypes to choose from. When the game begins the clock begins ticking until the next election at the end of year 4. Make sure to keep your resources balanced until the election campaign begins.</string>
    <string name="gameplay_gamefinish">To win the game you must ensure that you are elected to govern again. You must keep the people happy, the money flowing and your party stable to have a chance. When the game is over, please provide answers for the questionnaire. It requires no typing and will be used to evaluate the effectiveness of the game. </string>
    <string name="information">This application has been created as part of an Honours Project by a student at Abertay University. The game keeps track of how well you are progressing as it is played and sends this data to a server where it can be evaluated. To identify you the game makes use of your devices Android ID which is a secure and anonymous method recommended by Google itself. At the end of a game you must complete a questionnaire which will also be submitted to the server. This questionnaire asks for your age for no other reason than to verify that you are within the correct bracket for evaluation. Any information collected by the application will be used strictly for evaluation and will be removed from the server when the Project is finished. Thank you for taking time to read this information. If you require help in playing the game, please select Help on the main menu.</string>
    <string name="project_information">Project Description Goes Here.</string>

    <!-- Arrays for Government Type Spinners -->
    <string-array name="govtHoriz">
        <item>Collectivist</item>
        <item>Centrist</item>
        <item>Individualist</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="govtVert">
        <item>Authoritarian</item>
        <item>Moderate</item>
        <item>Libertarian</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Array for Engagement Answer Spinner -->
    <string-array name="engagement">
        <item>Not Engaged</item>
        <item>Slightly Engaged</item>
        <item>Engaged</item>
        <item>Very Engaged</item>
        <item>Actively Engaged</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Array for Age  Spinner -->
    <string-array name="age">
        <item>Younger</item>
        <item>18</item>
        <item>19</item>
        <item>20</item>
        <item>21</item>
        <item>22</item>
        <item>23</item>
        <item>24</item>
        <item>Older</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
